You always want to have
better experiences.  Menu understands that.  Therefore,
we are constantly striving to provide
better services every day.  Building upon the improvements to my contract page
, ManuLife proudly
introduces the ManuLife Vietnam app
for all customers, helping you
easily manage your insurance policy
and enjoy online services
anytime,
anywhere.  With just a few simple steps,
experiencing the features
is now easier, more convenient, and
faster with the Manol Vietnam app.
Biometric technology makes logging in incredibly
convenient.  The innovative features on the
Manol Vietnam app make managing your
insurance policy easier.  With just an
internet connection and a single tap to open the
Manol Vietnam app, you can inquire about your
insurance policy information
.  Request insurance claim processing
online.  Check the history and
status of your insurance claim
.  Look up and pay your insurance premiums
online.
Manage and update
personal information, register for online bank accounts
, withdraw dividends and cash vouchers,
or apply for loans
online.  View consultant information and
contact them directly, along with many
other service features.  With the Manualif Vietnam app
, experiencing services and managing
contracts online becomes even
better.  The Manual Vietnam app is now
available on the App Store and CHPL.  You're
ready to experience it.  Download the Manul
Vietnam app today to enjoy a
better life every day.
[Music]
[Applause]